{
    "subject": "resource/Hack_Schumann",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1884-08-13",
    "human_readable": "Hack Schumann was born on August 13, 1884.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8714709877967834,
            "question": "When was Hack Schumann born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8573265075683594,
            "question": "In what year was Hack Schumann born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7698028683662415,
            "question": "What is the significance of August 13th in Hack Schumann's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7593458890914917,
            "question": "Who is Hack Schumann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.736086905002594,
            "question": "What is Hack Schumann's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.54067462682724,
            "question": "Is there any information about Hack Schumann's life besides his birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3997595012187958,
            "question": "What can we learn about Hack Schumann's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35809215903282166,
            "question": "August 13th, 1884, falls on what day of the week?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32186079025268555,
            "question": "Does Hack Schumann have any notable achievements or accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2977156639099121,
            "question": "Can we find more details about Hack Schumann online?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hack Schumann was born on August 13, 1884.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1329_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Hack Schumann have any notable achievements or accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1329_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=August 13th, 1884, falls on what day of the week?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1329_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we learn about Hack Schumann's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1329_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1329_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents confirms that Hack Schumann was indeed born on August 13, 1884. This fact is mentioned in multiple documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1329/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1329/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the provided context information which explicitly states that \"Hack Schumann was born on August 13, 1884, in Buffalo, New York, United States.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}